<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chopin on</title><link>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/</link><description>Recent content in Chopin on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What's Chopin</title><link>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/introduction/</guid><description>Chopin by apio is a lightweight online store creator serveing lightweight online store web app with basic information and two Google Sheets (one for catalog and one for order).
Demo Go to demo store → Check out a 10-min Chopin demo video → Use Case There are many online store builders you can choose from. While the basic plan can be as low as $18 per month, these costs can add up quickly as the business grow.</description></item><item><title>Create New Store</title><link>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/create-new-store/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/create-new-store/</guid><description>Watch a three-minute tutorial video → 1. Open Chopin Stores Flow Go to Chopin Store Flow on Telescope . Log in with your Google account.
⚠️ Click Sign in with Google instead of entering email and password 2. Name the Store ⚠️ Store name cannot be changed later, but you can always create a new store. The name will be shown on top of the store.</description></item><item><title>Product Configuration</title><link>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/product-configuration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/product-configuration/</guid><description>By default, your store would look like below. We are pretty sure you&amp;rsquo;re not selling Cool Cat and Funny Cat.
To add and update products, go to your catalog google sheet.
catalog google sheet Edit product details by updating the following fields on the catalog google sheet:
⚠️ There should not be any empty line(s) between rows. ⚠️ Only items with valid name and price will be shown on your store.</description></item><item><title>Multi Option Products</title><link>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/multi-option-product-configuration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/multi-option-product-configuration/</guid><description>This is especially helpful if you are selling:
Clothes with different colors and sizes Food with different flavors Crafts with different patterns Events with different dates Checkout Demo Boutique Store → To configure multi option products, simply add the following columns to the catalog google sheet:
option:name option:size option:flavor option:color Review basic catalog google sheet configuration → Supported Option Display There are 3 multi option display styles and you can configure up to 2:</description></item><item><title>Store Configuration</title><link>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/store-configuration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/store-configuration/</guid><description>How to create a Chopin store → After the store is created. Go to Chopin App on Telescope to add customization and configuration for your store. You can update this information anytime (except store name and waitress APIs) and the updates will be reflected in real-time.
Click (save sign) to save your updates. Click (trash can sign) to delete the store completely. Click (plus sign) to add new information and click (minus sign) to delete the information.</description></item><item><title>Order Settings</title><link>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/order-settings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/order-settings/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t see a customization that fits your need? Drop us a message → Order Settings User Input Fields Determine what information you&amp;rsquo;d like to collect at checkout page.
By default, we only require customers to input in their email. You can check Hide box to eliminate certain fields or check Require box to make certain fields mandatory.
Name Email Phone Number Address Note 💡 We recommend using note field to collect customization details (i.</description></item><item><title>Payments</title><link>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/payments/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/payments/</guid><description>Each payment method will appear as a button on your store. If you don&amp;rsquo;t add any payment options, there will be a &amp;ldquo;Submit Order&amp;rdquo; button. You can enable as many payment options as you&amp;rsquo;d like.
Jump to payment method options → Visit our Demo Store and see how they work in real world. If you don&amp;rsquo;t see your preferred payment methods, drop us a message → Order Minimum Your customers' order total has to be greater than the minimum amount set to be able to place the order.</description></item><item><title>Contact Information</title><link>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/contact-information/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/contact-information/</guid><description>Contact Information Email The email address is default to the email you used to sign into Telescope. The email address is also used to send order confirmation emails. You can update to a different email.
How to Configure Order Confirmation Email → Facebook Full url to your facebook page or group (eg. https://www.facebook.com/apiobuild)
Instagram Instagram handle without @, not the full url (eg. apiobuild)
LINE 💡 Learn more how to create LINE url → url to your LINE account or LINE group.</description></item><item><title>Email Confirmation</title><link>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/email-confirmation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/email-confirmation/</guid><description>Post-It Permission Go to Post-It (apio's communication automation service) to authorize the Gmail account you&amp;rsquo;d like to send confirmation emails from. This app requires you to grant us permission to send emails on your behalf.
Click View Emails and then (plus sign) to add a Gmail Log in to your Google account Click Allow to grant apio access to send email on your behalf ⚠️ If you'd like to send emails from an account that's not the one you use to log in Telescope, be sure to update Email in Contact Information section.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting</title><link>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/troubleshoot/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://apiobuild.com/docs/docs/apps/chopin/troubleshoot/</guid><description>Not getting answers for your questions? Drop us a message → Catalog Google Sheet There should be no empty lines between rows. name of each product can not be empty nor can be characters other than numbers or alphabets. No spaces either. Product names must be unique. No products shown All products must have price and name otherwise they won&amp;rsquo;t be shown. Do not remove the existing catalog headers copied from tutorial.</description></item></channel></rss>